buyezee.net 2014-11-02

# BUYeZee Business Opportunity - Privacy Policay - Presented by BuyeZee LLC

## Privacy Policy

**INTRODUCTION**   
We (BUYeZee) take the privacy rights of users of the Websites ([http://BUYeZee.com](http://buyezee.com/) and http://BUYeZee.net) very seriously and are committed to protecting and respecting your privacy.  
This Privacy Policy is incorporated in and subject to the Terms of Use. By using the Website, you agree to the use of your Personal Information (as defined below) in accordance with this Privacy Policy. If you do not agree to this use, please do not use the Website or any of the services offered on the Website.

**WHO ARE WE?**   
Any Personal Information you provide to us is held by BUYeZee LLC a company registered in State of Delaware, in the United States of America with the company registration number 0523637.

**PERSONAL INFORMATION**  
“Personal Information” means any information about you which is personally identifiable which may include (but might not be limited to) your name, email address and any other information from which you can be identified and which you may disclose to us or otherwise via the Website at any time.

**WHEN DO WE COLLECT YOUR PERSONAL INFORMATION?**   
We may collect and process Personal Information when:  
• You provide Account Information when you register or sign in to your user account with us in order to use certain services such as the BUYeZee Newsletter or when you enter into any competition, promotion, prize draw or survey on the Website;  
• You view or buy a product or service from a merchant listing its offers on our Website;  
• You make a complaint or enquiry or provide feedback to us; or  
• You disclose Personal Information to us or through the Website at any point.  
• We will indicate where the provision of Personal Information is optional. If you choose not to provide such Personal Information you may find that some services or use of features of the Website are unavailable to you.

**HOW DO WE USE YOUR PERSONAL INFORMATION?**   
We may use your Personal Information in the following ways:  
• To process the registration and maintain the use of your account;  
• To allow you to participate in certain services such as BUYeZee Newsletter or any competition, promotion, prize draw or survey on the Website or to inform you of changes to any of these services;  
• To help us understand what products you have viewed or purchased through the Website in order to provide a better and more personalised service to you including advising of and offering products, services, content and special offers;  
• To analyse use of the Website including user demographics, interest and behaviour to optimise the services we offer;  
• To investigate any suspected breach of the Terms of Use by or relating to you;

**DO WE SHARE YOUR PERSONAL INFORMATION WITH THIRD PARTIES?**   
We may pass on your Personal Information to other parties as follows:  
• To select and trusted third parties who may use your Personal Information to serve you content that may be of interest to you. These third parties are not permitted to share or sell your information to anyone else;  
• To business partners to process the registration and maintain the use of your user account and to assist us in providing services to you. Such business partners are required to maintain the confidentiality of Personal Information and, unless you are otherwise advised, do not have any rights to use Personal Information that we provide to them for any purpose beyond what is necessary to assist us;  
• Some aggregated information about the Website users, sales patterns, traffic volumes and related matters to reputable third parties but these details will not include any information personally identifying you;  
• To the police, regulatory bodies or legal advisers in connection with any alleged criminal offence or suspected breach of the Terms of User or where required by law;  
• To any member of the BUYeZee group; and  
• In the event that we sell or buy any business or assets, in which case we may disclose Personal Information to the prospective seller or buyer of such business or assets.

**HOW DO YOU EDIT AND DELETE YOUR ACCOUNT INFORMATION AND PREFERENCES?**   
You can edit your account information and preferences at any time, including whether you want BUYeZee to contact you about products, services, content and special offers. If you do not wish to receive the BUYeZee Newsletter then you can also click on the link to unsubscribe contained at the bottom of the BUYeZee Newsletter email or email us.

**HOW LONG DO WE HOLD PERSONAL INFORMATION FOR?**   
We only hold Personal Information for as long as is necessary for the purposes described above in the paragraph headed “How do we use Personal Information?”

**HOW DO WE PROTECT PERSONAL INFORMATION?**   
We employ all industry standard practices and have strict security procedures covering the collection, storage and disclosure of Personal Information in order to prevent unauthorised access and to comply with relevant International data protection laws. All Personal Information you provide to us is stored on our or our business partners’ secure servers. The secure servers encrypt all Personal Information you input before it is sent to us. Where we have given you (or where you have chosen) a password which enables you to access certain parts of our site, you are responsible for keeping this password confidential. We ask you not to share a password with anyone.

**WHAT ARE COOKIES AND WEB BEACONS AND HOW DO WE USE THEM?**   
A cookie is a small amount of information which is sent to your browser from a website’s computers and stored on your computer’s hard drive. A web beacon is a small image (usually embedded in a web page or email) that allows a web site to count users who have visited that page or to access certain cookies. These tracking devices help us to improve our Website and to deliver a better and more personalised service. We have set out more detail on our use of cookies in our Cookie Policy.  
You may refuse to accept cookies by activating the setting on your browser which allows you to refuse the setting of cookies. However, if you select this setting you may be unable to access certain parts of our Website. Unless you have adjusted your browser setting so that it will refuse cookies, our system will issue cookies when you log on to our Website and, by continuing to use our Website, you agree to our use of those cookies as described  in our Cookie Policy.

**WHERE DO WE STORE PERSONAL INFORMATION?**   
We hold Personal Information on servers in the UK and USA. We hold and transmit your Personal Information in accordance with this privacy policy and applicable International data protection laws.

**ACCESS TO INFORMATION**   
You have the right to access information held about you. If you would like to receive a copy of your Personal Information held by us, please write to us at Legal Department, BUYeZee LLC, 1013 Centre Road, Suite 403-A, Wilmington, DE 19805, USA. We may charge you a small administrative fee to meet our costs in providing you with details of your Personal Information which we hold.

**CHANGES TO OUR PRIVACY POLICY**   
Any changes we may make to our privacy policy in the future will be posted on this page. This privacy policy was last updated on 21 August 2014.

**POSTING PERSONAL INFORMATION ON PUBLICLY ACCESSIBLE AREAS**   
A publicly accessible area of the Website is any area that is accessible by the general public and may be indexed by search engines. You are solely responsible for any Personal Information that you disclose and disseminate on publicly accessible areas. You should never disclose Personal Information relating to any other person without their express consent.

**OTHER LINKS**   
Our Website may, from time to time, contain links to and from the websites of our partner networks, advertisers and affiliates. If you follow a link to any of these websites, please note that these websites have their own privacy policies and that we do not accept any responsibility or liability for these policies. Please check these policies before you submit any of Personal Information to these websites.

**WANT TO KNOW MORE?**   
If you have any questions or comments about our privacy policy or how we use your Personal Information, please contact us by email or write to us at: Legal Department, BUYeZee LLC, 1013 Centre Road, Suite 403-A, Wilmington, DE 19805, USA
